microcenter.com 2010-03-26

# Micro Center Privacy Policy

This page discloses the privacy policy of Micro Electronics, Inc., Micro Center® and Micro Center Online®. We are concerned about your privacy and the security of your important personal information. We want you to be aware of what kind of information we obtain from you, how we use this information, and how you can control its use. By using this site or making purchases at our stores, you consent to this Privacy Policy. You should also review our Safe Shopping Promise for online purchases.

Micro Electronics, Inc. operates retail stores and web sites under the names of Micro Center® and Micro Center Online®. Micro Electronics, Inc. is the parent company of these companies, and as such, when you provide information to any of these entities, this information may be combined or shared between current or future Micro Electronics, Inc. entities and subsidiaries. 

This site is restricted to users from the United States and those not governed by privacy policies of the European Union. Users from the European Union are advised not to disclose personal information on this site. 

How is personally identifiable information collected?  
Customer information is collected during sales transactions primarily for customers in our stores through our in-store checkout process and other in-store contacts such as sweepstakes or contest entry forms.   Information is collected through online checkout process and for customers who register at our online Preference Center.   

On August 28, 2009, Micro Center acquired the postal mailing list of Circuit City Stores.   
Customer information is also collected through Micro Center’s acquisition of Circuit City’s customer database.  We will advertise to selected people in this group to encourage in-store and/or online purchases from us, and will solicit information from these customers when they buy from us, or want to voluntarily sign up for our mailing lists.

To opt-out of any communications from Micro Center, our Marketing Partners or other companies, refer to the opt-out sections below. 

What personally identifiable information is collected?  
In order to provide you superior service, communicate marketing promotions which we believe will be of interest to you, and to administer our business, Micro Center® retail  stores and Micro Center Online® may gather the following personal information (except where prohibited by law): salutation, name (first/middle/last), billing and shipping addresses, company name (if applicable), email address, phone/fax number (if applicable), payment type (VISA, Check, Cash, etc.), credit card type/number/expiration date. How this information is used and how we protect information collected from online purchases is explained below.

How is the collected information used?  
Micro Center® retail stores and Micro Center Online® use your personally identifiable information to provide superior service in the following areas: to process, fulfill and track online orders and in-store pickup reservations; bill your credit card for purchases; respond to your customer service inquiries or requests; provide requested services such as rebate redemption and warranty coverage; offer information regarding products and services based on your interests or past purchases; hold contests, giveaways, drawings and promotions; administer shopping or reward club accounts; conduct and administer surveys; mail marketing/sales material via email or postal mail; set up commercial accounts; sign up for new credit card promotions; or use it for other general business purposes to further enhance our business relationship with you.

To enhance your Micro Center Online® experience, we may also collect aggregate information as to which pages you visit, search terms used, etc. - in order to measure the effectiveness of our website and identify areas for improvement (product selection, site performance and/or to streamline the purchasing processes).

How do we use cookies and technology in our website?  
Micro Center Online® sets a cookie on your computer to record certain information during your online visit (session). No personally identifiable information is stored within this cookie. The benefit to you is the ability to save items added to your Shopping Cart and store them on our server for future reference (up to 30 days). These cookies do not gather sensitive information like your name, address, credit card number, etc., if you do not specifically give that information to us voluntarily. If you have given us that information, cookies enable us to recall it (and save you the trouble of entering it all over again) each time you visit our site.

Our web server collects the addresses of the web sites that visitors came from before visiting our site, which browser was used to view our site and search terms entered on our site. Without making use of any personally identifiable information, we may track the pages visited to help us understand how customers use our site. This helps us make decisions on how to create a better experience for you in the future.

At your option, if you delete our cookies, you will limit our ability to personalize the site for your next visit. However, deleting a cookie will not prevent you from visiting our site and making purchases.

Who are the third party entities with whom we may share your personally identifiable information? 

Third party service providers:  
Micro Center® retail stores and Micro Center Online® may provide your name, address and email address to reputable organizations that help us to fulfill services to you on our behalf. For example, we may use such third party service providers to authorize credit card transactions, ship packages, schedule and perform product installations, administer service programs, help us maintain records and analyze sales data, augment and improve the accuracy of our customer database and distribute postal and email communications to you with our offers or important information on our behalf. None of these third party service providers are authorized to use your information for any purpose other than to provide the above stated services for which they contract with us to perform. 

Marketing partners:  
Additionally, to enhance your computing experience with us, we may sponsor on a limited basis relevant offers from a very limited number of reputable marketing partners who provide special services or products that may be of interest and value to you, including financial institutions, warranty service providers and other entities with which we have an ongoing business relationship. We may provide these marketing partners personally identifiable information obtained from you, and this information may be combined with other personally identifiable information, such as demographic information, available from our records and other sources. However, we will NOT provide any of your financial or credit card transaction information or phone numbers to our marketing partners. Also, we will NOT provide your email address to our marketing partners unless you have given your authorization by checking "Subscribe" to "Marketing Partners" on the [preferences page](https://f.microcentermail.com/asbs/servlet/SS?F=2790827) of this website. We will not otherwise re-sell or distribute your email address to any third party.

**Other Companies - (applies to former Circuit City customers who have not made purchases from Micro Center Stores or Micro Center Online)**  
We are respectful of your preferences concerning the amount and source of mail you receive and that it is of interest to you. With this in mind, we may occasionally share your name, postal mailing address and purchase category information on a limited basis with a few trusted companies that we believe would offer products or services you would value as a purchaser of consumer electronics and similar types of products. We never share eMail addresses, telephone numbers or credit card account numbers with any of these third-party companies. If you would prefer that we not share your address information with outside companies, you may so indicate as noted in the opt out section below.

How do I unsubscribe from Micro Center sharing my information with other companies?  
There are various methods for letting us know if you would not like to receive postal mailings from other companies. ( **Important Note:** if you decide to unsubscribe from receiving mail promotions from other companies, this means we no longer provide your address to them. You will need to opt out of their specific promotions that you no longer want to receive via their unsubscribe process. Opting out of partner promotions directly will only opt you out of the promotions from them.)

  1. Go to our [preference page](http://f.microcentermail.com/asbs/servlet/SS?F=3285960) where you can unsubscribe to "Sharing Information". 
  2. Write to us and let us know what you would like to receive or not receive. You can send your letter to:  
**Communications Department**  
4119 Leap Road  
Hilliard, Ohio 43026  
**Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request. 
  3. Email us at [csrs@microcenterorder.com](mailto:csrs@microcenterorder.com)   
**Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request. 
  4. [Call Customer Support](http://www.microcenter.com/customer_support/contact_us.html). 

How do I opt in/out of Micro Center® and Micro Center Online® emails or postal mailings?  
There are various methods for letting us know if you would or would not like to receive Micro Center® and Micro Center Online® postal or email promotions. (Please note that if you opt out of our email marketing communications, you may still receive business-related communications such as order and shipping confirmations, product recall information or other administrative communications.)

  1. Go to our website (www.microcenter.com) and click on the [Email Newsletters](https://f.microcentermail.com/asbs/servlet/SS?F=2790827) link on the bottom of the home page. This will take you to our email options page where you can sign up to receive our various marketing promotions or request to no longer receive specified marketing promotions. 
  2. All promotional emails we send you contain a link allowing you to opt out of these specific emails in the future. Click on the relevant link and follow the simple instructions.
  3. Write to us and let us know what you would like to receive or not receive. You can send your letter to:  
**Email Communication Department**  
4119 Leap Road  
Hilliard, Ohio 43026  
**Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address, phone number and email address and tell us specifically which type of marketing communication you wish to receive or stop receiving. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request.   

  4. Email us at [csrs@microcenterorder.com](mailto:csrs@microcenterorder.com)   
**Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address, phone number and email address and tell us specifically which type of marketing communication you wish to receive or stop receiving. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request.   

  5. Call Customer Support.  

  6. While visiting our retail stores, request to get on our mailing lists.   

If you opted out of receiving our postal or email marketing communications, please allow us a reasonable period of time to honor your request, as some promotions may already be in process. For email subscriptions, please allow up to 10 business days for us to make the requested changes. Removal from our print advertising list may take up to 4 - 5 weeks, depending on the mailing cycle updating process.

Of course, you always have the option to get back on our mailing lists. Simply, go to our website ( www.microcenter.com ) and click on the [Email Newsletters](https://f.microcentermail.com/asbs/servlet/SS?F=2790827) link on the bottom of the home page. 

How do I opt in/out of Micro Center Marketing Partner emails?  
To enhance your computing experience with us, we may sponsor on a limited basis, relevant offers from a very limited number of marketing partners. We provide our marketing partners the names and email addresses of those who opted in to receive marketing partner emails on a per campaign basis (the list of opt in names is not provided for unlimited use by our marketing partners).

There are various methods for letting us know if you would or would not like to receive emails from our marketing partners. (Important Note: if you opt in to receive our marketing partner emails and you later decide to opt out, this means we will no longer provide your email address to them from that point forward. You will need to opt out of their specific email promotions that you no longer want to receive via their opt out processes. Opting out of their email promotions directly will only opt you out of the promotions from them.)

  1. Go to our website (www.microcenter.com) and click on the [Email Newsletters](https://f.microcentermail.com/asbs/servlet/SS?F=2790827) link on the bottom of the home page. This will take you to our email options page where you can make the choice to receive or not receive our marketing partner emails. It's a fast and easy process. 
  2. Write to us and let us know what you would like to receive or not receive. You can send your letter to:  
**Email Communication Department**  
4119 Leap Road  
Hilliard, Ohio 43026  
**Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address, phone number and email address and tell us specifically which type of marketing communication you wish to get or stop receiving. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request. 
  3. Email us at [csrs@microcenterorder.com](mailto:csrs@microcenterorder.com)   
**Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address, phone number and email address and tell us specifically which type of marketing communication you wish to stop receiving. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request. 
  4. Call Customer Support.  

We will only share your email address and other personally identifiable information with our marketing partners for emailing purposes if you authorized us by opting in.

Additionally, each email message our partners send you should include similar descriptions of simple opt in and opt out processes to enable you to stop receiving future email and marketing materials from them or their marketing partners. Please be aware that the sites operated by our marketing partners may collect personal information about you and will operate according to their own privacy practices that may differ from our Privacy Policy and our Safe Shopping Promise. Remember to consult other sites' privacy policies if you are concerned how your information is used by any party other than Micro Electronics, Inc. or Micro Center Online®. Also, you need to consult other sites' privacy policies to find out how to choose not to receive marketing information from companies other than Micro Electronics, Inc. or Micro Center Online® if that is your desire.

How do I unsubscribe from Micro Center Marketing Partner postal promotions?  
There are various methods for letting us know if you would not like to receive postal mailings from our marketing partners. ( **Important Note:** if you decide to unsubscribe from receiving mail promotions from our marketing partners, this means we no longer provide your address to them. You will need to opt out of their specific promotions that you no longer want to receive via their unsubscribe process. Opting out of partner promotions directly will only opt you out of the promotions from them.)

  1. Go to our [preference page](https://f.microcentermail.com/asbs/servlet/SS?F=2790827) where you can unsubscribe to the marketing partners. 
  2. Write to us and let us know what you would like to receive or not receive. You can send your letter to:  
**Email Communication Department**  
4119 Leap Road  
Hilliard, Ohio 43026  
**Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to our marketing partners. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request. 
  3. Email us at [csrs@microcenterorder.com](mailto:csrs@microcenterorder.com)   
**Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to our marketing partners. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request. 
  4. Call Customer Support.

How do we protect the security of your Micro Center Online® order information?  
Micro Electronics, Inc. and Micro Center Online® are concerned about your privacy and the security of your important personal information. We always use industry standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving any data that you exchange with our site. We employ the same industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that is used by major banks and stock brokerage firms to conduct business via the Internet. This encryption procedure "scrambles" the information you send us and makes online transactions extremely safe.

When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information, such as financial information, you will be redirected to a secure server and we will notify you, depending on the type of browser you are using, through a pop-up screen or a yellow "padlock" icon displayed in the lower portion of the browser window. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you via this site.

For complete details, please see our Safe Shopping Promise.

How do we handle information related to children?  
This site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly or intentionally obtain any personally identifiable information from any person we know to be under the age of 13.

How can you contact us with questions regarding this Privacy Policy?  
If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by writing to: Micro Center Online at 4119 Leap Road, Hilliard, Ohio 43026 or calling Customer Support. Please remember to include your postal address, email address and phone number with your correspondence.

How am I notified of Privacy Policy changes?  
As we continue to grow our businesses and improve our services, we reserve the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If there are changes or additions, we will post those changes here or in other formats we deem acceptable, so that you are aware of such changes. If this Privacy Policy changes in such a way that your personally identifiable information may be used or shared in a different manner, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of having your information used or shared in that new manner. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please check back at this site periodically. 

Disclosure exceptions:  
Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary: to comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website and/or Micro Center Online®; to protect Micro Electronics, Inc.'s rights and property; or during emergencies, such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk.

In addition, as we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer information, email addresses, and visitor information are generally among the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution, including, but not limited to, a bankruptcy proceeding.

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is May 28, 2002. It was last updated on November 19, 2009.
